Office of Communications and Marketing Records UA252
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Public Relations files, 1964 -- 2015; UA252.001; 6 Linear Feet
  - GDAE, 2006 -- 2007; UA252.001.004.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Genzyme, 1998-11 -- 1999-04-20; UA252.001.004.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - GMAP, 2000-12-28; UA252.001.004.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Provost Website, 2003-01-15 -- 2003-02-05; UA252.001.004.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Public Relations, 2001-08-30 -- 2002-05-01; UA252.001.004.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Tufts Public Health, 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.004.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Public Safety, 1999-09-01 -- 2004-10-01; UA252.001.004.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - President Speeches, 1999-03-16 -- 1999-11-04; UA252.001.004.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Quinn's Foundation, 2001-03-08; UA252.001.004.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Religion, 2002-03-05; UA252.001.004.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - NESCAC, 2001-09-27; UA252.001.004.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - New Faculty, 2000-08-30 -- 2000-08-31; UA252.001.004.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Neustadt, Mark, 2005-11-18; UA252.001.004.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - JUMBOt, 2003-05-14; UA252.001.004.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Kaleidoscope, 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.004.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Peace and Justice Studies, 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.004.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Photos, 2000; UA252.001.004.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Physics and Astonomy, 2001-06-04; UA252.001.004.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Political Science, 2000-11-07 -- 2002-05; UA252.001.004.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - PR Clips, 2005-09-15; UA252.001.004.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - President General 2007, 2007-04-27; UA252.001.004.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - President General 2005, 2005-02-04; UA252.001.004.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - President General 2000, 2000-06-29 -- 2000-09-12; UA252.001.004.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Music Dept., 2006-04 -- 2007-02-08; UA252.001.004.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Mystic River, 2001-10-03; UA252.001.004.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Events: Match Day, 2008-09-10; UA252.001.004.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Nancy & Tonya Opera, 2006-04-10; UA252.001.004.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Medford, City of, 2002-02; UA252.001.004.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Marshall Scholarship, 2001-12-07; UA252.001.004.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Malden Project, 2000-02-24 -- 2000-06-20; UA252.001.004.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Marathon 2004, 2003-04-21; UA252.001.004.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Marathon 2005, UA252.001.004.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Long. Health Study, 2001-05-03; UA252.001.004.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Murrow Collection, 2007-04-09; UA252.001.004.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Linda Abriola, 2004-07-30; UA252.001.004.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Research: CSDD, 2001-11-30; UA252.001.004.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Research: TLHS, 2000 -- 2002-01-28; UA252.001.004.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Romance Languages, 2000 -- 2001; UA252.001.005.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Romaro/Galapagos Islands, 2001-06-19; UA252.001.005.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Rooftop Garden, 2006-12-15; UA252.001.005.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Senior Stories, 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.005.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - SIS, 2012-03 -- 2012-04; UA252.001.005.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Somerville, City of, 2001-11-16 -- 2013-02-28; UA252.001.005.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Brand: Stonebridge, 2000-10-12 -- 2001-03-06; UA252.001.005.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Sustainable Dev. Summit, 2002-08-26 -- 2002-09-04; UA252.001.005.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Systems, 2013; UA252.001.005.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Technology, 2007; UA252.001.005.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - TIE, 1999-04-24 -- 2001; UA252.001.005.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Tisch College, 2007-02-15; UA252.001.005.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - TERAC Report, 2003-01-28 -- 2003-01-31; UA252.001.005.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Tisch Library, 2010; UA252.001.005.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Trustee Reports, 2004-08-05 -- 2012-12; UA252.001.005.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - UCCPS, 1999-02 -- 2002-02-07; UA252.001.005.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Undergrad. Task Force, 2002-12-04; UA252.001.005.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - University Relations, 2014-04 -- 2014-09; UA252.001.005.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - University Seminar, 2008 -- 2009; UA252.001.005.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Urban & Enviromental Policy, 2004 -- 2005; UA252.001.005.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Vet School PR, 2005-05-05 -- 2005-09; UA252.001.005.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Brand, 1999-08-11 -- 2000-01; UA252.001.005.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Forums: HR Documents, 2003-04-04; UA252.001.005.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - 150th Anniversary, 2001-06-08 -- 2002-04-19; UA252.001.005.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Tamasanis-Commencement, 1996-09-18; UA252.001.005.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Hollister-Dean, 1996-09-18; UA252.001.005.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Fawaz-Dean, 1996-09-18; UA252.001.005.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Tisch Opening, 1996-09-18; UA252.001.005.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Smoking & Tooth Loss, 1996-09-16; UA252.001.005.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Equine Health Seminar, 1996-09-18; UA252.001.005.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Gordon Inst./Asia, 1996-09-19; UA252.001.005.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Kosch Reception, 1996-09-23; UA252.001.005.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Hopes On Music Industry, 1996-09-23; UA252.001.005.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Woodstock Clinic, 1996-09-24; UA252.001.005.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Sex Hormones and Breast Cancer, 1996-09-25; UA252.001.005.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Philippine Conference, 1996-09-25; UA252.001.005.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Roman Perseus, 1996-10-03; UA252.001.005.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Transgenic Corn, 1996-10-04; UA252.001.005.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Rosenberg Nutrition, 1996-10-04; UA252.001.005.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Whitecoat Ceremony, 1996-10-08; UA252.001.005.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Food & Physique, 1996-10-09; UA252.001.005.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Rabies, 1996-10-11; UA252.001.005.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Telemedicine, 1996-09-27; UA252.001.005.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - CSDD Course, 1996-10-15; UA252.001.005.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - AOA - Feng, 1996-10-17; UA252.001.005.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Life Games, 1996-10-18; UA252.001.005.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Day Care Yard Sale, 1996-10-21; UA252.001.005.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Baker Bullets, 1996-10-22; UA252.001.005.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Lupus & Homocystein, 1996-10-22; UA252.001.005.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Flood & Mold, 1996-10-23; UA252.001.005.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Helping Kids Behave, 1996-10-25; UA252.001.005.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Baker-Fares Lecture, 1996-10-25; UA252.001.005.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Tau Neutrino, 1996-10-30; UA252.001.005.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Baker Fares Lecture, 1996-10-30; UA252.001.005.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Autopsies, 1996-11-15; UA252.001.005.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Lourie Overseer, 1996-11-15; UA252.001.005.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Levine Overseer, 1996-11-15; UA252.001.005.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Full Professors, 1996-11-19; UA252.001.005.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Skin Stretcher, 1996-11-20; UA252.001.005.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - International Thankgiving, 1996-11-21; UA252.001.005.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Miller Hometown, 1996-11-21; UA252.001.005.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Miller Clinic, 1996-11-21; UA252.001.005.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Deborah Digges, 1996-11-25; UA252.001.005.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Ethics Panel, 1996-11-25; UA252.001.005.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Cold Fusion, 1996-11-27; UA252.001.005.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Harrington Hometown, 1996-12-02; UA252.001.005.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Harrington DeaN, 1996-12-02; UA252.001.005.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Folate, 1996-12-10; UA252.001.005.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Mothers Carry Fetal Cells, 1996-12-11; UA252.001.005.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Bill Richardson, 1996-12-02; UA252.001.005.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Alumni Leaders, 1996-12-11; UA252.001.005.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Artificial Foot, 1996-12-18; UA252.001.005.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Vet Open House, 1996-08-13; UA252.001.005.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Organ Transplants, 1996-08-16; UA252.001.005.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Voter Registration, 1996-08-19; UA252.001.005.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Kerry At Tufts, 1996-08-30; UA252.001.005.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - US News Rankings, 1996-09-05; UA252.001.005.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - The Big E, 1996-09-05; UA252.001.005.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Equine Encephalitis, 1996-09-17; UA252.001.005.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 79)
- Trustees files, 1953 -- 2008; UA252.002; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains files about Tufts Trustees compiled by the Office of Communications and Marketing. Files include photographs, newspaper clippings, correspondence, biographical information, and other materials.
  - Trustees Group Photos - '88, 1988 -- 1994-01-11; UA252.002.006.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Charles F. (Trustee), 1976-03-22; UA252.002.006.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Aidekman, Shirley (Trustees), 1996; UA252.002.006.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Arango, Placido, 1996; UA252.002.006.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Baronian, J. (Trustees/Members), 1969-12 -- 2008-04-29; UA252.002.006.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Bell, W. Douglas (Trustees/Members), 1976-01-20 -- 1976-02-03; UA252.002.006.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Behrakis, George (Overseer), 2001; UA252.002.006.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Bergstrom, Joan, 1999-09; UA252.002.006.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Berenberg, Roslyn (Trustee), 1983-05-26 -- 1987; UA252.002.006.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Berger, L. (Trustees/Members), 1996-08-14; UA252.002.006.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Bernstein, I. (Trustees/Members), 1971-02-23 -- 1977-04-29; UA252.002.006.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Blount, Stephen (Trustees), 1993; UA252.002.006.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Brooks, H. (Trustees/Members), 1981-01-14 -- 1981-02-27; UA252.002.006.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Brown, P. (Trustees/Members), 1986; UA252.002.006.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Budd, Ed (Trustees), 1996 -- 1997; UA252.002.006.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Burn, B. (Trustees/Members), 1984-05-17 -- 1984-05-31; UA252.002.006.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Burns, M. (Trustees/Members), 1974-01-02 -- 1986; UA252.002.006.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Trustees/Bylaws, 1968-11-27 -- 1975-12-01; UA252.002.006.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - L. Cabot, John G. H.D., 1984-02-07 -- 1984-03-01; UA252.002.006.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Callow, A. (Trustees/Members), 1976-01-09 -- 1987-03-02; UA252.002.006.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Trustees/Candidates, 1967-11-10 -- 1978-02-01; UA252.002.006.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Cardozo, A. (Trustee), 1984-12-12; UA252.002.006.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Carley, W. (Trustee), 1980; UA252.002.006.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Carr, Kenneth L. (Trustee), 1994-08-31 -- 1995-04-19; UA252.002.006.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Chayet, N. (Trustees/Members), 1971-05-18 -- 1982; UA252.002.006.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Cohen, Robert S. (Trustee Emeritus), 1998; UA252.002.006.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Cummings, Bill (Trustees), 2004-08-21; UA252.002.006.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - de Burlo, R. (Trustees/Members), 1953-03-05 -- 1979; UA252.002.006.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Trustees/Committees, 1967-02-07 -- 1980-06-01; UA252.002.006.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Dowling, John, 1987 -- 2000; UA252.002.006.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Fares, Isam M. (Trustees), 1987; UA252.002.006.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Florence, Leonard (Trustees), 2000-12-06; UA252.002.006.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Foster, H., 1983-06-15; UA252.002.006.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Trustees/General, 1966-12-19 -- 1983-08; UA252.002.006.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Gelb, Leslie (Trustees), 1984-02-07 -- 1998; UA252.002.006.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Gifford, N. (Trustees/Members), 1993 -- 1996; UA252.002.006.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Gilbert, C. (Trustees/Members), 1961-01 -- 1984; UA252.002.006.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Goldberg, C. (Trustees/Members), 1973-02-05 -- 1973-12-14; UA252.002.006.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Gordon, Bernard, 1996-11-21 -- 1999-11; UA252.002.006.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Hallian, W. (Trustee), 1964; UA252.002.006.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Hauck, Frederick H. (Trustee), 1987-08-10; UA252.002.006.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Heneghan, J, (Trustees/Members), 1980-10-01; UA252.002.006.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Howard, J. (Trustees/Members), 1971-07-06 -- 1973-12-17; UA252.002.006.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Howland, W. (Trustees/Members), 1964-11-20; UA252.002.006.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Jaharis, Michael (Trustees), 2000; UA252.002.006.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Krol,John A, (Trustees), 2000; UA252.002.006.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Leach K. (Trustees/Members), 1996-09-26; UA252.002.006.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Legvold, Robert (Trustees), 1987; UA252.002.006.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Lewiton, J. (Trustees), 1987; UA252.002.006.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Littleton, E. (Trustees/Members), 1974-07-08 -- 1974-07-11; UA252.002.006.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - MacPhie, E. (Trustees/Members), 1977; UA252.002.006.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Marvin U. (Trustees/Members), 1975-01-02 -- 1984; UA252.002.006.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Mastrovita, Robert (Trustees/Members), 1981-12-28; UA252.002.006.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - McFarlane, A. (Trustee), 1966-11-15 -- 1996-04-29; UA252.002.006.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - McGrath, David III (Trustee), 2000; UA252.002.006.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - McMahon, W. (Trustees/Members), 1970-08-07 -- 1975-01-02; UA252.002.006.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Merrin, E. (Trustees/Members), 1987; UA252.002.006.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Merrin, Seth (Trustees), 2005-01-27; UA252.002.006.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Meserve, Robert (Trustee), 1964-10 -- 1995-09-25; UA252.002.006.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Mesereve, William (Trustee), 1984-06-21 -- 1989-02; UA252.002.006.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Neubauer, Joseph, 2000; UA252.002.006.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - O'Brain T. (Trustees/Members), 1987; UA252.002.006.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Omidyar, Pierre (Trustees), 2001; UA252.002.006.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - O'Neill, John T. (Trustees), 1980; UA252.002.006.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Pres. Search Committee (Trustees), 1970-09 -- 1976-03-01; UA252.002.006.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Remis, R. (Trustees/Members), 2000; UA252.002.006.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Richardson, Kenneth D., 1986; UA252.002.006.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Saltonstall, William H.D., 1976; UA252.002.006.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Sargent, H. (Trustee), 1973-12-19; UA252.002.006.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Reid, Inez Smith (Trustees), 1993; UA252.002.006.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Sackler, Jill (Trustees), 1993; UA252.002.006.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Sellers, William (Trustees), 1992 -- 2000-11; UA252.002.006.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Sher, Joann G. (Trustees), 1993; UA252.002.006.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Silverman, Norman (Trustees), 1996-11-21 -- 1997; UA252.002.006.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Smith, J. (Trustees/Members), 1974-04-11 -- 1974-04-21; UA252.002.006.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Stephanian, Ira (Trustees/Members), 1981-10-23 -- 1982-11-24; UA252.002.006.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Stern, Jim (Trustees), 1984-05-17 -- 1999-12-02; UA252.002.006.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Tanenbaum, Morris (Trustees/Members), 1977-03 -- 1982-02-14; UA252.002.006.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Tarr, Robert J. Jr. (Trustees), 1993; UA252.002.006.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Thomson, C. Admin (Trustees/Members), 1965 -- 1973-11-15; UA252.002.006.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Tisch, Preston, 1996; UA252.002.006.00081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Tisch, Jonathan (Trustees), 1996-10-16; UA252.002.006.00082; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Tishler, M. (Trustee), 1969-12-15 -- 1987-07-16; UA252.002.006.00083; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Toon, M. (Trustees/Members), 1980-10-06 -- 1987; UA252.002.006.00084; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Vargus, Dr. Ione D. (Trustees/Members), 1980-10-27; UA252.002.006.00085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Varis, Agnes (Trustee), 2000 -- 2005-01-27; UA252.002.006.00086; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Winkler, Thomas F. (Trustee), 1999 -- 2000-12-06; UA252.002.006.00087; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Winnick, Gary (Trustee), 1995-11-07 -- 1995-11-13; UA252.002.006.00088; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Wood, Gordon S. (Trustees), 1992 -- 1993; UA252.002.006.00089; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Wren, Paul (Trustee), 1980-01-17 -- 1983-05-26; UA252.002.006.00090; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Weiant, E. (Trustees/Members), 1974-06-28 -- 1979-06-01; UA252.002.006.00091; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 91)
- Photograph and publicity files, 1861 -- 2016; UA252.003
  This series is open for research.
  This series contains files about Tufts schools, buildings, events, people, and groups compiled by the Office of Communications and Marketing. Files include photographs, newspaper clippings, publications, event programs, press releases, speeches, and other materials.
  - Aidekman Arts Center, 1973 -- 2003; UA252.003.007.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    photos
  - Aidekman- Betrayal of Means, 1993; UA252.003.007.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Aidekman- Breaking the Mold, 1991 -- 1993; UA252.003.007.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Aidekman- Hiroshima, 1998; UA252.003.007.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Aidekman- No Laughing Matter, 1983 -- 1990; UA252.003.007.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Aidekman- Rescuers of the Holocaust, 1992; UA252.003.007.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Aidekman- Rothenberg exhibit, 1994; UA252.003.007.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Aidekman- "Visual Contact", 1992 -- 1993; UA252.003.007.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Aidekman- Warsaw Ghetto, 1941 -- 1992; UA252.003.007.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 9)
    photos/exhibit program
  - AIDS Quilt, 1992; UA252.003.007.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - African-American Center, 1982 -- 1992; UA252.003.007.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Alumni- Arts and Sciences, 1970 -- 2006; UA252.003.007.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 12)
    photos/newspaper clippings
  - Alumni- Dental, 1985 -- 1989; UA252.003.007.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Alumni- Medical, 1986 -- 1987; UA252.003.007.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Alumni- Vet School, 1987 -- 1991; UA252.003.007.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Anderson Hall, 1960 -- 1969; UA252.003.007.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 16)
    photo
  - Anti-Gravity Stone, 1961; UA252.003.007.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Architecture- Design Shots, 1962 -- 1973; UA252.003.007.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 18)
    photos/building desgins
  - Arena Theater, 1964 -- 1991; UA252.003.007.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 19)
    photos/press release
  - Art, 1986 -- 1991; UA252.003.007.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - A&S Book Party, 2005; UA252.003.007.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Arts&Sciences- Donors, 1994 -- 1997; UA252.003.007.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 22)
    photos/magazine clipping
  - Asian American Center, 1991 -- 1992; UA252.003.007.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Athletics, 1983 -- 2004; UA252.003.007.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 24)
    photos/press releases
  - Athletics- Basketball, 1995 -- 2003; UA252.003.007.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 25)
    photos/event programs
  - Athletics- Chase Gymnasium, 1997; UA252.003.007.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Athletics- Crew, 1985 -- 1991; UA252.003.007.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Athletics- Cross Country, 1998 -- 2000; UA252.003.007.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 28)
    photos/newspaper clipping
  - Athletics- Fitness Center, 1993; UA252.003.007.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Athletics- Football, 1949 -- 2004; UA252.003.007.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 30)
    photos/letter/newspaper article
  - Athletics- Ice hockey, 1979 -- 2003; UA252.003.007.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 31)
    photos/emails/floppy disc
  - Athletics- Indoor sports, 1988; UA252.003.007.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Athletics- Sailing, 1989 -- 1993; UA252.003.007.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Athletics- Soccer, 1994 -- 2000; UA252.003.007.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 34)
    photos/newspaper clippings/event program
  - Athletics- Swimming, 1987 -- 1998; UA252.003.007.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Athletics- Track and Field, 1994 -- 2000; UA252.003.007.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Athletics (women), 1986 -- 1994; UA252.003.007.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Athletics- women's track, 1984 -- 1989; UA252.003.007.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Bacow Inaugural, 2002; UA252.003.007.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 39)
    CDs/programs/press release/address
  - Ballou Hall, 1997; UA252.003.007.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Baronian Field House, 1950 -- 2000; UA252.003.007.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 41)